<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

	<RK_Scenario_Refugee.label>Ratkins who ran away to escape the world</RK_Scenario_Refugee.label>
	<RK_Scenario_Refugee.description>In the Ratkin Kingdom, dissatisfied with the power centered around the king and nobles, the Ratkins rose up in revolt, seeking to overthrow the monarchy and establish a new system where the citizens would lead the nation. 
However, as time passed, the civil war continued unabated. In addition to the barbaric royalists, who were hostile to and invaded other foreign powers inhabiting the planet, the rebels were now divided into two factions, each with its own competing interests. 
Since their initial uprising against the Ratkin Kingdom, the rebels (revolutionaries) have strived to minimize the casualties of innocent civilians caught up in the fighting and have widely publicized their reasons for rebelling against the Kingdom to various factions. Because they fight against the Kingdom with funds earned only through legal means, and because they avoid barbaric acts like conscripting child soldiers or exploiting civilians, they have received significant support from various factions on the planet. However, another faction, split off by internal strife, tarnishes the very name "revolutionary army." 
They generate funds through various illegal activities, such as drug trafficking, and supplement their income with plunder and massacre. They even kidnap young Ratkins and use them as child soldiers, using them as cannon fodder. The original purpose of overthrowing the monarchy and replacing it with a republic has disappeared, and they have degenerated into a corrupt group of warlords and a gang of trashy bandits who only think about filling their own stomachs by any means necessary, regardless of their own interests. 
Disillusioned by this bleak and miserable reality, some Ratkins decided to join like-minded individuals and find a new home for themselves. Of course, they all carried crossbows to prepare for danger, and even "obtained supplies secretly during the civil war, when both sides were fighting furiously."</RK_Scenario_Refugee.description>
	<RK_Scenario_Refugee.scenario.description>In the chaos of civil war, I walked tirelessly for days, carrying only what I could, trying to survive. Finally, I found a new haven, a safe haven. However, the psychological scars remain unforgettable... I remember the screams echoing alongside gunfire in the street battles, the explosions of shells falling from the Royalist and Republican armies, the screaming ratkins fleeing, and the mothers weeping as they held their children, killed by shells... 
    And while fleeing, I was greeted by the horrific sight of my own people, a pile of cold corpses, at the site of the plunder and massacre of innocent Ratkins by a disgusting warlord organization that defiled the identities of my people... I'd like to forget if I could, but the indelible wounds echo within me. 
Anyway, when will the civil war end? Will the sun ever shine in my rat hole? I must first recover from my mental wounds and exhaustion, then devise a plan to build a hideout.</RK_Scenario_Refugee.scenario.description>
	<RK_Scenario_Refugee.scenario.summary>With the civil war between the Ratkin Kingdom and the rebels continuing unabated, the disillusioned Ratkins decided to go their own way.</RK_Scenario_Refugee.scenario.summary>

</LanguageData>